Local 1199 Additional Records 5871
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Additional Records
1986-1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU)
RWDSU Local 1199 Drug, Hospital & Health Care Employees
5871
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5722556
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 08, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5206: Local 1199 Records 5525: Local 1199 Additional Files 5510: Local 1199 Records 5651: Local 1199 Additional Records 5680 OH: Local 1199 Oral History Project 5854: Local 1199 Additional Records 5928: Elaine Leeder Collection of Rose Pesotta Papers 5938: Local 1199 Leon Davis Additional Papers
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.); Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union
5722556
- 1986 Election UP Newspaper Save Our Union (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Speeches - 1199 Newspaper - Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Election Press (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1984 Election UP Election Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Campaign Press, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Election and NLRB (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1199 Legal (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1199 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Betty Hughley (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Elections w/ 1199 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Elections, "Unity Programs Slate" (Box 1, Folder 11)
- D. Turner Lit., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- G. Johnson Info. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- G. Johnson Info. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- void (Box 1, Folder 14)